

Software Engineer seeking assignments in Software Development, Application Programming, Program Management, Full Stack Development, Requirement Gathering, ASP. Net MVC, Entity

Framework, LINQ, Javascript, ADO. Net, JQuery, C#. Net, TFS, VSTS, MS SQL Server



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 9 Month(s)

Current Company: Mobien Digital Pvt. Ltd (Inva Systems Inc) Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: MCA [engineering]

Pref. Location: Ahmedabad, Mumbai, Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Program

Management, Gap Analysis, Full Stack Development, Requirement Gathering, ASP. Net MVC, Entity

Framework, LINQ, Javascript, ADO. Net, JQuery, C#. Net, TFS, VSTS, MS SQL Server

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

ASP.Net MVC Developer

Developed full-stack web applications which processed, analyzed, and rendered data visually.

.Net Framework experience in analysis, designing, development, debugging and maintenance of 3-tier enterprise Web Application

Developing application using .NET 4.5/ 4.0/ 3.5, MS Visual Studio, Razor View Engine, C#, ASP.Net MVC, Web API, JSON,

AJAX, HTML5 and CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Entity Framework, LINQ, SQL Server, Web services.

Coordinated with technical teams for project for preparation of specific section of programs. Supported technical team members for designing and development of custom software solutions.

Proficiency in Mappings to achieve connection between relational databases.

Enthusiastic, Ability to quickly understand and utilize new technologies

Wrote business logic in C# to handle transactions from and to database using ADO.NET objects such as Data Sets, Data Adapters, and Data Readers.

Work Experience

Mobien Digital Pvt. Ltd (Inva Systems Inc) as Software Engineer

Jan 2018 to Till Date

Tools and Technologies at work: ASP.NET MVC, C#, SQL Server, Web API, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, VSTS, Ajax, Entity Framework, LINQ.

Project name: Vinmar Pricing. Period: March 2018 to April 2018

Team size: 4

Technology: ASP.NET MVC, C#, Web API, Entity Framework, LINQ, SQL Server 2014, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Ajax, Json, VSTS.

Responsibilities: All Ui Design responsibility and decisions, help for database design, Coding, debugging.

Project Description: SAP pricing will allow regional and corporate manages visibility and trends on the sell price of all products. The selling price of each order will be compared to minimum sale price (MSP) and the MSP will be specific to a product and region. The comparison will allow managers to analyze a trend and conduct a market analysis for various regions and business. This in turn will allow the business to rank customers on various measures such as willingness to pay.

Project name: Vinmar EDS.

Period: 09 May 2018 to 11 Jan 2019

Team size: 4

Technology: ASP.NET MVC, C#, Web API, Entity Framework, LINQ, SQL Server 2014, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Ajax,

Json, VSTS.

Responsibilities: All Ui Design responsibility and decisions, help for database design, Menu rendering as per user role,

Coding, debugging.

Project Description: EDS stands for Expert Documentation System. Which 4 involves integrations with SAP, AES, ELOG and DMS. We get various data from SAP using consuming RFC's dumps all valid data into database. Based on amount of SO we assign LC (Letter of Credit). Created various document(s) based on delivery which can be sent to various

department(s). Based on created document we archive the created document into DMS systems. And then passes to AES

for exporting actuals goods to outside the US.

Project name: Vinmar BI. Period: 15 Jan 2019 to present

Team size: 7

Technology: ASP.NET MVC, C#, Web API, Entity Framework, LINQ, Flex-monster, SQL Server 2014, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Ajax, Json, VSTS.

Responsibilities: All Ui Design responsibility and decisions, Design and develop dashboard as per user role, database design, Coding, debugging, Implement Flex-monster tool on this project, load data for Service analysis Cube to flex-monster, User can design develop graph and set dashboard.

Project Description: BI stand for Business Intelligence. This project user creates a multiple reports and dashboard summary. User allowed which column are show on report and remove reports.

Swift Techno Crafts Pvt Ltd as Software Developer

Feb 2016 to Dec 2017

Tools and Technologies at work: ASP.NET MVC, C#, SQL Server, Web API, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, TFS, Ajax

Project name: Event Management System. Period: 11 May 2017 to 30 Dec 2017

Team size: 3

Technology: ASP.NET MVC, C#, Web API, SQL Server 2014, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Ajax, Json.

Responsibilities: Design of the Web pages, Menu bars, design of database, coding, debugging.

Project Description: The EMS provides functionality to manage any commercial or non-commercial events. The proposed

EMS system will consist of a web-based, centralized database for client management and reporting.

Education

UG: BCA (Computers) from Shivaji University, Kolhapur in 2012

PG: MCA (engineering) from Pune University in 2015

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
C#.NET, ADO.NET	
ASP.NET MVC, HTML5, CSS3	
JavaScript, and jQuery, Angular	
Dapper, Web API, TFS, VSTS, Bootstrap	
Entity framework, LINQ	
MS-SQL Server 2016/2014/2012/2008/2005	
MS-Access	
Visual Studio 2017/2015/2012/2010/2008	
SQL Server	
Magneto, WordPress	
Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Windows XP, Linux	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization